[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the major equations of relativity.", "correct_answer": "E=M*C^2", "incorrect_answers": ["V=(4/3)*pi*r^2", "V=arcsine(pi+i^2)", "L=sqrt(L/g)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not  a prime number?", "correct_answer": "1", "incorrect_answers": ["13", "3", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fibromyalgia is a disorder of the central nervous system.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is the Angel Falls, the highest waterfall on the planet, located?", "correct_answer": "Venezuela", "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "Argentina", "Colombia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following terms refers to the abnormal fear of walking or standing erect?", "correct_answer": "Basiphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Basistasiphobia", "Stasibasiphobia", "Stasiphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1990, this movie received the Academy Award for Best Picture at the 62th Academy Awards ceremony.", "correct_answer": "Driving Miss Daisy", "incorrect_answers": ["My Left Foot", "Born on the Fourth of July", "Dead Poets Society"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor played three different roles in Stanley Kubricks 1964 movie Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb?", "correct_answer": "Peter Sellers", "incorrect_answers": ["George C. Scott", "Slim Pickens", "Sterling Hayden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "12 x 2 +(6/4) ^2 equals what?", "correct_answer": "26.25", "incorrect_answers": ["576", "666", "56.25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays Lucy Dawson at the age of 3?", "correct_answer": "Elle Fanning", "incorrect_answers": ["Trisha Fanning", "Dawn Fanning", "Dakota Fanning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What record did the 1937 animated movie Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs set?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["It was the first full-length feature film be produced by Walt Disney.", "It was the first full-length celluloid-animated feature film.", "It was the first full-length feature film produced in full color."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nickname Queen State has been given to this U.S. state.", "correct_answer": "Maryland", "incorrect_answers": ["West Virginia", "Virginia", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The word adeno, deriving from Greek, refers to which to what body part?", "correct_answer": "Gland", "incorrect_answers": ["Flesh", "Brain", "Kidney"]}]